

# Oleksandr Likvytskyi

Front-end Developer

# **CONTACT**



+48 733 819 952



alex eastwoody@yahoo.com



https://eastwoodyl1c.github.io/web /



linkedin profile

# **ABOUT ME**

I have big experience in my life, graduated as an engineer in renewable sources of energy, then I moved to Poland and living here at this moment working in factories. Now i decide, i have to change my life and as i wanted before, went into the IT specialty. I got skills as a front-end developer and continue to improve my skills in this way.

#### **LANGUAGES**

English - Intermediate Polish - Intermediate Russian - Native Ukrainian - Native

# **EDUCATION**

#### **Kherson National Technical University**

Renewable energy sources. Electrical engineering and electrotechnologies

2010/2015

#### **Lemon School**

Front-end (HTML/CSS + JS) Developer 10.2022/02.2023

#### **Lemon School**

JavaScript Development

02.2023/06.2023

#### **Lemon School**

ReactTS

06.2023/----

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

JSC "Khersonoblenergo" | 2017-2018 Engineer

Voss Automotive Poland Sp. o.o. | 2019 - 2020 Production operator

Lear Corporation | 2020 - 2022

Production operator

C+P Sp.z o.o. | 2022 - 2023

Welder operator